{
    "id": "3427f2ee2931480d89830ba5f9503660",
    "title": "Exclamations Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "How charming ……………………….!",
            "description": "In exclamations the subject goes before the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "is she",
                "she is",
                "she does"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bed1bb3ed11e4ace90dc2d3e00d31a29"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. lovely morning it is!",
            "description": "Use what a before adjective + noun.",
            "answers": [
                "What a",
                "How",
                "How a"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e1b49233a29642c797136edd9fd5a8df"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… tall she has grown!",
            "description": "Use how before an adjective without noun.",
            "answers": [
                "What a",
                "How",
                "How a"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "900b05f63cba43e1944b1b82397680ce"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… beautiful house you have!",
            "description": "Use what a before adjective + noun. ",
            "answers": [
                "How",
                "What a",
                "How"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4ca179ba9fd84fa6827ef60702353897"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… quickly the holidays passed!",
            "description": "Use how before adjective or adverb.",
            "answers": [
                "What a",
                "What",
                "How"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a2d896ebb95e42b9b897d6c19722e008"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. fool he is!",
            "description": "Use what a before a noun or noun + adjective. Use how before an adjective or adverb.",
            "answers": [
                "How",
                "How a",
                "What a"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1db2cd2fb75c4b9fa31e43710f13abda"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. tragedy!",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "How a",
                "What a",
                "How"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "64aa3db8e3f14b52aae78795552d91ca"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. brilliant idea it was!",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "How",
                "What a"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "99dc0b4a8976429cb83c54b02a6f9201"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… clever girl she is!",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "How",
                "What a"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e620af866cbc48ff864178d6855890d0"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… well she dances!",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "How",
                "What",
                "What a"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "634a6f389b8f42d09609579e79e71f61"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… sweet the mangoes are!",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "How",
                "What a",
                "How a"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "177a20b86a7b4ce98ae58b1812f954ae"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… beautifully she sings!",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "How",
                "How a",
                "What a"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "15c939f7c6a547ffa19883d4e7cc0867"
        }
    ]
}